Hello everyone
Welcome to my channel
Today I'd like to share some thoughts and insights on the use of AI
First of all
Get straight to the point
I believe all of us in the younger generation should go all in on AI.
This is the opportunity that belongs to our generation.
At this point, a significant number of people would consider AI to be nothing more than a chatting tool.
Not enough to stir up much of a storm
This is a completely wrong understanding of AI
as long as you take a little time to understand AI in depth
you'll find it's an absolutely groundbreaking technology
This holds true for any organization or individual alike.
In my opinion
AI has permeated every aspect of my life.
My studies and daily life are inseparable from this technology now.
If I had to go without using AI for two days
My academic life will come to a standstill
If we have already realized the importance of AI
So how should we learn AI?
We are influenced by exam-oriented education.
It's easy to fall into such a misconception
Thinking that we must take learning AI seriously
Spend a lot of time in the library studying various aspects of AI
The history of AI development
All that useless AI knowledge crap
This is the flawed learning model that schools have imprinted upon us.
We must learn to shed this outdated
torturous learning mode
The way we learn should involve fully utilizing AI in our daily lives.
any questions
Any thoughts
Explore every project with AI to see if it sparks new innovations
instead of learning through those outdated models that old professors have been using for over a decade
We should use AI to reshape our learning methods
This way you can experience the profound joy of progress.
Last but not least, this is something I particularly want to emphasize.
Learn to use AI to tackle all the bullshit work in college
Universities are filled with all sorts of meaningless nonsense.
a waste of energy
tormenting and stifling personal growth
various tasks that stifle human creativity
Find a way to use AI to tackle these tedious tasks
free up more time
Free up more energy to think about the issues you consider important
Learn what you consider important knowledge
a person's energy
Time is the most precious asset one has
It's not those damn tasks.
Fake credits
Also, if any school assignments prohibit the use of AI
Or limit the use of AI
Then there's a 99% chance this task is already outdated.
AI can easily replace it.
The old evaluation system can no longer filter or screen effectively through this.
But the old evaluation system has inertia.
has a time lag
They won't let you pass these task evaluations so easily.
Take the thesis for example
If an undergraduate student can meet the standards of a graduation thesis with the help of AI
Then why waste more effort obsessing over those words?
Spending a ton of energy interacting with advisors to produce content universally acknowledged as meaningless for students' long-term development
Then why not let AI assist in solving these tasks?
Calling it training students' abilities is all bullshit.
You should know that the ability to write papers
Long ago, it became utterly meaningless for students' personal development in society.
Now, with the added impact of AI, this is even more the case.
The more essential skill to master is the in-depth utilization of AI.
instead of being stuck in this distorted evaluation system
neither here nor there
We should think outside the box
Exploring the possibility of a breakthrough
instead of being constrained by all sorts of old rules that stifle judgment and creativity